Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 2, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Working at Brownan Equal Opportunity Employer, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 69)
    Author: Brown University
- Box: 2, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Applied Anthropology Problems of Human Organization, 1946; Publication (Box 2, Folder 70)
    Author: S. Buchsbaum and Co.
- Box: 2, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Careers With A Future, Publication (Box 2, Folder 71)
    Author: Buckeye Cellulose Corporation
- Box: 2, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Academic Organization, 1963; Publication (Box 2, Folder 72)
    Author: Bucknell University
  - Item 2: Employee Information, 1967; Publication (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Box: 2, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Buffalo Business, 1959; Publication (Box 2, Folder 73)
    Author: Buffalo Chamber of Commerce
  - Item 2: Buffalo Business, 1959; Publication (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Box: 2, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: The Syracuse Plan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 74)
    Author: Building Industry Minorities Employment
- Box: 2, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: List of Members-Officers Board of Governor's Committees, 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 75)
    Author: Building Trades Employer's Association
  - Item 2: List of Members-Officers Board of Governor's Committees, 1954; Publication (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Box: 2, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Integrity: Basis of Effective Labor Relations in Building Industry, 1949; Publication (Box 2, Folder 76)
    Author: Building Trades Employer's Association of NYC
- Box: 2, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Welcome, Publication (Box 2, Folder 77)
    Author: The Bullard Company
  - Item 2: Application for Employment, 1951; Publication (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Item 3: Telephone Check List, 1954; Publication (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Box: 2, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Triple Protection with Your "Better Job", 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 78)
    Author: Bullard Co.
  - Item 2: Security After the "Better Job', 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Item 3: Security After This "Better Job", 1951; Publication (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Box: 2, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Series on Pointers for Office Supervisors, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    Author: Bureau of National Affairs
- Box: 3, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The 1965-1966 Panel of BNA's Personnel Policies Forum (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Information Services for Business and Professional Use, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Filmsfor Management Development, Supervisory Training, and Employee Communications, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The 1959-1960 Panel of BNA's Personnel Policies Forum (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: The BNA Story, 1957; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Author: Dean Dinwoodey
  - Item 6: The 1955 Panel of BNA's Personnel Policies Forum, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: The 1953 Panel of BNA's Personnel Policies Forum, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: BNA Briefiing Sessions on Background for Bargaininga Series of Two Day Conferences in Washington, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Box: 3, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Burlington Review, 1974; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Author: Burlington Industries Inc.
- Box: 3, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The New Force in Politics, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Author: Business Industry Political Action Committee
  - Item 2: Individual Political Action!, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: The New Force in Politics, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: A New Force in Politics: An Interview, 1964; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Author: Arthur H. (Red) Motley
    Notes: Reprinted from The Journal of American Chamber of Commerce ExecutivesApril
  - Item 5: Newsletter, 1964; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: Number 3 Aug.
- Box: 3, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Employee's Retirement Benefit Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Author: Butler Manufacturing Company
    Notes: Jan. 1, 1951
- Box: 3, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Our Company, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Box: 3, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Butte County Employer-Employee Relations Laws and Regulations, 1970; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Author: Butte County, CA
- Box: 3, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: You and Your Bank, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Author: California Bank, Los Angeles
- Box: 3, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Management Manpower Requirements State of California, 1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Author: Comission on California State Govn. Org. and Economy
- Box: 3, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Health and Welfare Report, 1969; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Author: California Council for Health Plan Alternatives
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 3 Aug. 1969
  - Item 2: Health and Welfare Report, 1969; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 2 July
  - Item 3: Health and Welfare Report, 1972; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: Jan. 14, 1972
  - Item 4: Health and Welfare Report, 1972; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 15 Dec. 1, 1972
- Box: 3, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Disability Insurance Provisions, 1963; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Author: California Department of Employment
- Box: 3, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Recent Publications of the Division of Labor Statistics and Research, 1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Author: California Dept. of Industrial Relations
  - Item 2: Functions of the Department of Industrial Relations, Including Legal Obligations and Responsibilities of All Divisions, 1963; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: Nov. 1
  - Item 3: Index of Recent Publications, 1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: California State Conciliation Service, 1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: California State Conciliation Service, 1963; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Industrial Relations, 1959; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Industrial Relations, 1960; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: Aug.
  - Item 8: Report to Governor's Council, 1963; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Introduction to Department of Industrial Relations, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Box: 3, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Wage Settlements: California Union Agreements, 1969; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Box: 3, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Welcome Kit, 1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Author: California Dept. of Mental Hygiene
  - Item 2: For All Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Box: 3, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: State Plan for Vocational Rehabilitation, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Author: California Dept. of Rehabilitation
  - 1966, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Box: 3, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: California Apprenticeship Council, 1962; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Author: California Div. of Apprenticeship Standards
  - Item 2: Apprenticeship for Skill: Your Key to Economic Progress, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Craftsmanship Through Apprenticeships, 1958; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Box: 3, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Rules of Practice and Procedure, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Author: California Division of Industrial Accidents
- Box: 3, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Usted Tiene El Derecho, 1962; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Author: California Fair Employment Practice Commission
    Language: Spanish.
  - Item 2: Whoever You Are, 1964; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: You Have the Right, 1962; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Fair Employment Law in California: Your Rights Your Responsibilities, 1960; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Success Story, 1963; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Promoting Equal Job Opportunity, 1964; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Si Se Puede!, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Language: Spanish:English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, 1950; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Author: California Metal Trades Association
- Box: 3, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Improving Management Performance, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Author: California Personnel Management Association
  - Item 2: Publications of the California Personnel Management Association, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Box: 3, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Report of the Senate Fact Finding Committee, 1963; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Author: California Senate Legislature-Fact Finding Committee on Labor Welfare
- Box: 3, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Adjustment of Labor-Management Disputes in California, 1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Author: State of California Department of Industrial Relations
- Box: 3, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Your Retirement Plan and Related Benefits, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Author: California State Employee's Retirement System
  - Item 2: Information for State Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Information for Classified School Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Box: 3, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Information on Supplemental Health Benefits Plans for Age 65 Employees, Annuitants and their Dependents, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: The State Employees' Medical and Hospital Care Act, 1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: The State Employees' Medical and Hospital Care Act, 1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Box: 3, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Supervisor's Handbook: A Guide to Employee Discipline, 1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Author: California State Personnel Board
  - Item 2: A Proposed Approach for Formalizing Employer-Employee Relations in the State Civil Service, 1969; Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Notes: Jan. 24
- Box: 3, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Cooperative Personnel Services, 1950; Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Box: 3, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Harvest, 1975; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Author: Campbell Soup Company
- Box: 3, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: A Career in Professional Law Enforcement May Be Yours in the California Highway Patrol, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Supervisor's Handbook: Sick Leave Administration, 1969; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Careers in California State Government, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: Personnel Research in the California State Service, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Box: 3, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Personnel Rules for Nonacademic Employees, 1964; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Author: California University
  - Item 2: Working for the University, 1968; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Box: 3, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: A Talk Delivered Before Labor Audience, 1951; Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Author: William Gomberg
  - Item 2: Institute of Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Box: 3, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Handbook for Faculty Members of the University of California, 1968; Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Box: 3, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Author: California University Institute of Industrial Relations
    Notes: Vol. 9, No. 1 May 3 copies
  - Item 2: Bulletin, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 9, No. 2 Nov. 2 copies
  - Item 3: Bulletin, 1968; Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 10, No. 1 May 2 copies
  - Item 4: Bulletin, 1970; Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Item 5: Newsletter, 1975; Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Item 6: Newsletter, 1975; Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Item 7: Newsletter, 1975; Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Box: 3, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Service Conditions and Benefits, 1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Author: Canada Civil Service Commission
  - Item 2: Careers for University Graduates with the Government of Canada, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 3: Careers for University Graduates with the Government of Canada, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 4: Careers for the Bachelor Graduates in the Physical Sciences, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 5: Careers for Graduates in Engineering with the Government of Canada, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 6: Careers for University Graduates with the Government of Canada, 1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 7: Careers for Bachelor Graduates in Bio Sciences with the Government of Canada, 1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 8: Careers for University Graduates with the Government of Canada Law, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 9: Careers for University Graduates with the Government of Canada Medical Sciences Dietetics Social Work, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Box: 3, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Publication (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Box: 3, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Your Superannuation Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Author: Canada Dept. of Finance
- Box: 3, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: The Case of the Missing COG, Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Author: Canada Department of Labor
  - Item 2: The Door to Service, 1960; Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Recent Developments in the Work of the Dominion Bureau of Statistics, 1961; Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Box: 3, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Recent Developments in the Work of the Dominion Bureau of Statistics, 1964; Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Author: Canada Dominion Bureau of Statistics
  - Item 2: Recent Developments in the Work of the Dominion Bureau of Statistics, 1962; Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Item 3: Recent Developments in the Work of the Dominion Bureau of Statistics, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Box: 3, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: History of the national U.I.C. Association, Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
    Author: M.P. Fitzpatrick
- Box: 3, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Council of Graphic Arts Unions of the Public Service of Canada, 1968; Publication (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Author: Canada Treasury Board
- Box: 3, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Your Suggestion System, Publication (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Author: Canadair
  - Item 2: Ideas Pay Off, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Item 5: Benefits that Can Result From a Well Administered Suggestion System, Publication (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Box: 3, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: 3rd Quarter Progress, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Author: Canadian Electric Co. Limited
- Box: 3, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 3, Folder 41)
    Author: Canadian General Electric Company
- Box: 3, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Contact the C-I-L Newspaper, 1955; Publication (Box 3, Folder 42)
    Author: Canadian Industries Limited
    Notes: Vol. 24, No. 1 Jan
- Box: 3, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Summary Report on Personnel, 1927; Publication (Box 3, Folder 43)
    Author: Canadian National Railways
  - Item 2: Report on Survey of Personnel, 1927; Publication (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - 1927, Publication (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Box: 3, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan, 1959; Publication (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Item 2: Benefit Plan for Employees of Canadian Railways, 1959; Publication (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Box: 3, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Publication (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Item 2: Staff Welfare Plans, 1968; Publication (Box 3, Folder 45)
    Author: Carleton University
  - Item 3: Employment Hours of Work Leave Policy, 1968; Publication (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - 1968, Publication (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Box: 3, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: You and Your Job, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 46)
    Author: Carlisle Corp.
- Box: 3, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Setting Up a Proven Management Alignment Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 47)
    Author: Carnegie Illinios Steel Corp.
- Box: 3, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Organization and Faculty Policies, 1967; Publication (Box 3, Folder 48)
    Author: Carnegie- Mellon University
- Box: 3, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Basic Facts About the Carpet and Rug Industry, 1953; Publication (Box 3, Folder 49)
    Author: Carpet Institute
- Box: 3, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Careers, Publication (Box 3, Folder 50)
    Author: Carrier Air Conditioning Co.
- Box: 3, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Affirmative Action News, 1977; Publication (Box 3, Folder 51)
    Author: Carrier Corporation
  - Item 2: View, 1978; Publication (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Item 3: View, 1977; Publication (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Item 4: View, 1977; Publication (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Item 5: View, 1977; Publication (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Box: 3, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Carrier Suggestion System, Publication (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Box: 3, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Non-Academic Personnel Policy Manual, 1968; Publication (Box 3, Folder 53)
    Author: Case Western Reserve University
- Box: 3, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: News from Caterpillar, 1975; Publication (Box 3, Folder 54)
    Author: Caterpillar Tractor Company
  - Item 2: Caterpillar World, 1969; Publication (Box 3, Folder 54)
    Notes: Dec./Jan.
- Box: 3, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Seven Pillars of Industrial Order, Publication (Box 3, Folder 55)
    Author: Francis J. Haas, D.D.
  - Item 2: A Traveling School of Social Thought, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 55)
    Author: Catholic Conference on Industrial Problems
  - Item 3: Portland Meeting of the Catholic Conference on Industrial Problems, 1950; Publication (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Item 4: Portland Meeting of the Catholic Conference on Industrial Problems, 1953; Publication (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Box: 3, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Suggestion System, 1958; Publication (Box 3, Folder 56)
    Author: Celatex Corp.
  - Item 2: Your Job and its Evaluation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Box: 3, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: News, 1969; Publication (Box 3, Folder 57)
    Author: Center for Community Change
    Notes: May 26
  - Item 2: News, 1968; Publication (Box 3, Folder 57)
    Notes: Dec. 22
  - Item 3: News from the Ford Foundation, 1968; Publication (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Item 4: Biography of Jack Thomas Conway, Publication (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Item 5: Board of Directors, Publication (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Box: 3, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: "I'm Not A Quitter!": Job Training and Basic Education for Women Textile Workers, 1991; Publication (Box 3, Folder 58)
    Author: Juliet Merrifield: Lachelle Norris: Loretta White
- Box: 3, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: A Program for Economic Growth, Publication (Box 3, Folder 59)
    Author: Center for the Study of Productivity Motivation
- Box: 3, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Supervisory Conference Program, 1951; Publication (Box 3, Folder 60)
    Author: Central Arizona Light and Power Co.
- Box: 3, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: When Oakland Was Young, Publication (Box 3, Folder 61)
    Author: Central Bank (Oakland)
- Box: 3, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Working with Central Hudson, Publication (Box 3, Folder 62)
    Author: Central Hudson Gas and Electric Corp.
- Box: 3, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Retirement and Separation Allowance Plan for Employees of Niagara Hudson System Companies, 1941; Publication (Box 3, Folder 63)
    Author: Central N.Y. Power Corp.
- Box: 3, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: How to Win Workers, Publication (Box 3, Folder 64)
    Author: Cessna Aircraft Company
- Box: 3, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Employee Merit Training, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 65)
    Author: Chamber of Commerce and Board of Trade of Philadelphia
  - Item 2: Handling Grievances, 1944; Publication (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Box: 3, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Key Note Address, 1967; Publication (Box 3, Folder 66)
    Author: Chamber of Commerce of Fort Wayne, IN
- Box: 3, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Classified List of Trade and Allied Associations and Publications in the City of New York, 1951; Publication (Box 3, Folder 67)
    Author: Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York
  - Item 2: Resolutions and Report Presented by the Committee on National Security, 1951; Publication (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Box: 3, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: New Suggestion Procedure Explained to Employees, Publication (Box 3, Folder 68)
    Author: Champion Paper and Fibre Co.
- Box: 3, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Grow with Charmin, Publication (Box 3, Folder 69)
    Author: Charmin Paper Product Company
  - Item 2: There's a Growing Future for You Grow With Charmin, Publication (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Box: 3, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Welcome to Chase, Publication (Box 3, Folder 70)
    Author: Chase National Bank
- Box: 3, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Employee Benefit Plans, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    Author: Chemical Bank New York Trust Co.
- Box: 3, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, 1958; Publication (Box 3, Folder 72)
    Author: Chemstrand Corporation
- Box: 3, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, 1959; Publication (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Item 2: Industrial Statesmanship at home and Abroad, Publication (Box 3, Folder 73)
    Author: Edward A. O'Neal, Jr.
  - Item 3: The Acrilan Fiber Plant, Publication (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Item 4: Annual Report, 1958; Publication (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Item 5: Chemical Week, 1958; Publication (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Item 6: Annnual Report, 1957; Publication (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Item 7: A Year of Progress, 1956; Publication (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Box: 3, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Employees' Benefit and Retirement Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 3, Folder 74)
    Author: Chenago & Unadilla Telephone Corp.